[{"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狗_L1.svg", "num": 6}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg", "num": 7}], "compareText": "少"}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg", "num": 6}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/海豚_L1.svg", "num": 8}], "compareText": "少"}], "answers": [2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg", "num": 6}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg", "num": 9}], "compareText": "少"}], "answers": [3], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg", "num": 6}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg", "num": 10}], "compareText": "少"}], "answers": [4], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg", "num": 7}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狗_L1.svg", "num": 6}], "compareText": "多"}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg", "num": 7}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg", "num": 8}], "compareText": "少"}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg", "num": 7}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg", "num": 9}], "compareText": "少"}], "answers": [2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/海豚_L1.svg", "num": 7}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狗_L1.svg", "num": 10}], "compareText": "少"}], "answers": [3], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg", "num": 8}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Left/熊_L1.svg", "num": 6}], "compareText": "多"}], "answers": [2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg", "num": 8}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/兔子_L1.svg", "num": 7}], "compareText": "多"}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg", "num": 8}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg", "num": 9}], "compareText": "少"}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg", "num": 8}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/松鼠_L1.svg", "num": 10}], "compareText": "少"}], "answers": [2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg", "num": 9}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg", "num": 6}], "compareText": "多"}], "answers": [3], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/松鼠_L1.svg", "num": 9}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Left/熊_L1.svg", "num": 7}], "compareText": "多"}], "answers": [2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg", "num": 9}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg", "num": 8}], "compareText": "多"}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg", "num": 9}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg", "num": 10}], "compareText": "少"}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg", "num": 10}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狗_L1.svg", "num": 6}], "compareText": "多"}], "answers": [4], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg", "num": 10}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg", "num": 7}], "compareText": "多"}], "answers": [3], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg", "num": 10}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/松鼠_L1.svg", "num": 8}], "compareText": "多"}], "answers": [2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "compare-count", "title": "选一选", "stem": "数一数，比一比", "list": [{"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg", "num": 10}, {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg", "num": 9}], "compareText": "多"}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["10以内数的大小比较"], "level": "2", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-11-03"}]